don't you dare touch my Sonic
Underground DVD again please I just want
to watch one episode this DVD is my most
prized possession if you so much as look
at it I will make you my [ __ ] laugh my
ass off but are you gonna do shove my
head up your ass if so I dare you please
shove my head up your smelly ass I'm
begging you you are making a grave
mistake by giving me your permission to
do so little man I will do anything to
watch Sonic Underground even if I must
become someone's [ __ ] you know what no
screw this I'm going to go watch Sonic
Underground right now you can't tell me
what to do
oh my God somebody help me
it sniffs Sonic Underground balls [ __ ]
Sonic Underground gives me strength
get over here [ __ ]
[ __ ] please is that really all you've
got I bet you don't even own the very
rare limited-edition Sonic Underground
plushies that were exclusively sold for
limited time at Denny's that may be true
but it doesn't belittle my love for
Sonic Underground
or how much I wanted to bang me in the
ass like the little Sonic Underground
[ __ ] I am get off of me [ __ ] I'm the
one who always wanted to be Sonic
Underground's a little bit more than you
ever did so sniff my smelly balls like
oh my God you leave me alone oh my God
help me take this [ __ ] oh my God
somebody help me
that's it I'm tired of this [ __ ] I'll
show you just how much I love Sonic
Underground even if I have to kill you
to prove it
get over here [ __ ] found you [ __ ]
stop fighting I have an idea that will
make all three of us heavy the TV show
that defines everyone's childhood the
last Sonic cartoon that was good before
modern Sonic sure took over we all loved
Sonic Underground just as much as each
other so there's no reason to fight yeah
Sonic Underground is sexy put the hammer
down
all right [ __ ] let's go watch Sonic
Underground at my place
you